pipelinedeals.com 2019-03-17

# PipelineDeals Privacy Policy | PipelineDeals

PipelineDeals, Inc. ("PipelineDeals") is committed to protecting your privacy. We take privacy very seriously here at PipelineDeals and post this PipelineDeals Privacy & Security Policy ("Policy") to explain our policy and what PipelineDeals does with the information we collect from you which may identify you (referred to in this Policy as "personal information") when you visit and use our website and the applications and services offered by PipelineDeals (the "Services").

### What Information We Collect:

Our vision at PipelineDeals is to introduce visitors to the benefits of our services and to facilitate contact management for all of our customers ("Account Holders") and our collection and use of your personal information is intended to help us achieve these objectives.

During your visit to the PipelineDeals website, we (or third parties acting on our behalf) may capture certain personal information about you:

  * upon sign up with PipelineDeals (for a trial or for purchasing the service), you may be required to provide your name, billing address, email address, password, and login id (which you create in the registration process);
  * we may capture your company name, billing phone number, time zone, date format, time format and credit card information so you may subscribe to and pay for the Service, but we do not store any credit card information. All credit card information is stored by a third party credit card processor. All recurring credit card charges (either monthly or yearly) are authorized in advance by the customer;
  * periodically, PipelineDeals may conduct webinars or other similar web events in which personal information may be collected (through our website or a third party service such as Citrix's Gotomeeting). In order to participate in such events, you are required to provide your name, email address, number of employees, and how you heard about the web event; and
  * PipelineDeals may capture the following personal information: address, phone number, industry, organization name and role in the purchase process.

Any personal information you or anyone with your login id and password upload into the Services in the form of files, contact information, industry knowledge, maps, financial information, and the like remains your sole and exclusive property, and we will not authorize any third party to access that personal information except pursuant to this Policy or where you have provided your explicit consent for us to do so. Please note that this information is also subject to the PipelineDeals Terms and Conditions of Use which may be found at: http://www.pipelinedeals.com/terms.

### Why We Collect Your Information:

We use personal information we collect about you or that you provide to us to:

  * present our website and its contents to you;
  * provide you with information, products or services that you request from us;
  * deliver or perform our products or services;
  * enhance or improve our products or services;
  * provide you with notices about your account;
  * provide the requested services and improve the website and deliver a better more personalized service to you;
  * carry out our obligations and establish, exercise or enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us which may include where we reasonably consider it is in our legitimate interests or the legitimate interests of others, or where we are legally required to do so;
  * in any other way we may describe when you provide the information; and
  * for any other purpose with your consent.

### Legal Basis for Use of Your Personal Information:

We consider that the legal bases for using your personal information as set out in this privacy policy are as follows:

  * our use of your personal information is necessary for our legitimate interests or the legitimate interests of others (for example, to ensure the security of our website). Our legitimate interests are to: 
    * Provide a business to business tool for Contact Relationship Management for our customers.
    * Provide a mechanism for businesses to contact and communicate with other businesses.
    * Provide product communications to our customers regarding product features and enhancements
    * Provide service status and outage information
    * Provide product training and tips.
    * Provide records of communication between PipelineDeals and our Customers to ensure customer satisfaction with our product.
  * our use of your personal information is necessary to perform our obligations under any contract with you (for example, to fulfill any order which you place with us, to comply with the terms of use of our website which you accept by browsing our website and/or to comply with our contract to provide services to you); or
  * our use of your personal information is necessary for complying with our legal obligations (for example, providing information to government tax authorities).

Other use may be subject to your consent (which can be withdrawn at any time after giving it, as described below). Where this is the case, that need for consent will be identified in this Privacy Policy.

### Website Navigational Tools and How they are Used:

As you navigate the PipelineDeals website (whether or not you register as a user), personal information may be collected automatically through the use of commonly used information gathering tools such as cookies (imbedded code that recognizes your browser), web beacons (clear electronic images that can recognize certain types of information) and other existing or future tracking technology. Additionally, we collect other information from your Web browser, such as browser type, your internet protocol address and actions you have taken on our website (i.e., pages viewed and clicked links).

Cookies are small text files that a website can write to your computer. We may use cookies to identify you and facilitate subsequent access to the website. Flash cookies are local stored objects on your computer that collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on the PipelineDeals website.

Web beacons are small electronic files that permit PipelineDeals to collect website statistics such as how many users visited the website. Such information is used to determine the popularity of certain website content and verify system and server integrity.

Internet Protocol Addresses are collected by PipelineDeals to track and aggregate non-personal information. These addresses are collected when you log in.

Where we use cookies on our website, you can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.

By continuing to use our website, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.

### Your Privacy with PipelineDeals:

PipelineDeals will never ask for your login id, password or any other personal information in an unsolicited phone call, email or letter. Should anyone contact you requesting such information, please contact PipelineDeals directly via email at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#42213731362d2f27302123302702322b32272e2b2c272627232e316c212d2f) to advise us. 

Further, any contact with PipelineDeals customer service in which personal information is exchanged with a customer service representative will be used only for the purpose of satisfying that request. Any personal information you provide to a customer service representative will not be recorded or used for any reason other than in accordance with this Policy or as directed by you.

### Your Privacy with Third Parties:

The PipelineDeals website may contain links to various other websites and enable interoperation of other applications and services that are not owned or controlled by PipelineDeals. Each of these other providers has a privacy policy that may differ from that of PipelineDeals. The privacy practices of such websites, applications and services not provided by PipelineDeals are not covered by this Policy. PipelineDeals does not endorse or otherwise accept any responsibility or liability for the content of such third party websites or third party terms and conditions or policies.

PipelineDeals will not disclose any of the personal information supplied to PipelineDeals to any other third party except as expressly mentioned in this Policy, the Terms and Conditions of Use or as directed by you.

### Our Policies on Email and Subscribing to the Service:

PipelineDeals does not support spamming over email by our Account Holders. If you would like to report an incident of email spamming, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#294a5c5a5d46444c5b4a485b4c695940594c4540474c4d4c48455a074a4644) We will investigate and take suitable action at our discretion. PipelineDeals may send you marketing and other email communications from time to time including special offers, new features, new products or services, and referrals. Any email from PipelineDeals will fully comply with the CAN-SPAM Act. In each of these emails, you will be given the choice to unsubscribe from the PipelineDeals communications by clicking on "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the email. In addition, if you do not wish to receive such emails you may specify your communication preferences to our customer service representatives at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#5b382e282f34363e29383a293e1b2b322b3e3732353e3f3e3a372875383436) or by calling +1 (866) 702-7303. Account Holders will always receive any system-wide notices regarding scheduling of maintenance that may or may not result in the Service being temporarily unavailable. Please note that Account Holders may not "opt-out" of receiving these emails. 

Choice of subscription to the Service is yours at all times, and you are free to remove yourself as an Account Holder at any time. Simply follow the directions in any of our emails.

### Forums, Chat, Blogs, and Customer Testimonials:

PipelineDeals may provide bulletin boards, blogs, or chat rooms on our website. Any personal information you choose to submit in such a forum may be read, collected, or used by others who visit these forums, and may be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these forums. Please understand that, though we may have some small influence over our Account Holders, we fundamentally cannot control the online or offline actions of our Account Holders or other parties, especially when it comes to their use of personal information that you choose to disclose in moderated or unmoderated newsgroups and forums, known on the PipelineDeals website as "Forums". While we will investigate complaints sent to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#e0839593948f8d859283819285a0908990858c898e858485818c93ce838f8d) and take appropriate action with our Account Holders or other parties, we will typically not provide any personal information to third parties about our conversations with our Account Holders. We encourage people to resolve disputes directly with each other and discourage people from attempting to use PipelineDeals to police their mailbox or newsgroup. 

### Referral Program:

PipelineDeals lists customer names, customer titles and testimonials from customers on its website. However, PipelineDeals never posts any such information without obtaining the consent of the customer prior to posting such information. Customers may elect to use PipelineDeals' affiliate program to refer and inform friends about the PipelineDeals website and services. When using the affiliate program, PipelineDeals requests the friend's name, email address and country. Using that information, PipelineDeals will send the friend an email inviting him or her to visit the PipelineDeals website and if they visit may send follow up emails.

By providing personal information of a third party, you are representing to PipelineDeals that you have all necessary authority and/or have obtained all necessary consents from such individual to collect, use and disclose his or her personal information as set forth in this Policy. If we receive a written complaint or direction from the person, we will delete his or her information and notify you that we have done so.

### Sharing of Personal Information Collected:

Only those PipelineDeals employees trained in our security processes with managerial oversight would ever have access to your personal information which includes your name and login id. Our employees will not have access to your password. If you forget your password, you will be able to use our fully automated password recovery system to help you gain access to your account.

We may use contractors or vendors to help us provide some of the services at our website. If we need to disclose personal information to them in order to provide these services, it is with the requirement that the personal information is kept confidential and is used only for those services. Any third parties with whom we share your personal information are limited (by law and by contract) in their ability to use your personal information for any purpose other than to provide services for PipelineDeals. We will always ensure that any third parties with whom we share your personal information are subject to privacy and security obligations consistent with this Policy and applicable laws.

PipelineDeals may provide access to your personal information to a successor of PipelineDeals in connection with a sale, merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of the assets of the business, whether as a going concern or as part of a bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding. PipelineDeals reserves the right to use or disclose your personal information if required by law or if PipelineDeals reasonably believes that use or disclosure is necessary to protect its rights and/or to comply with any laws including a judicial proceeding or court order.

We may also disclose your personal information to enforce or apply our services agreement, and other agreements (including for billing and collection purposes), for any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the personal information (and for which we have a legal basis) or where you have provided your consent for us to do so.

### Customer Data:

While you may electronically submit data and information (which may include personal information) to the PipelineDeals Service for hosting and processing purposes, PipelineDeals will not review, share, distribute or reference any of your data or information except as provided in the Terms and Conditions of Use, this Policy, or as may be required by law.

### Location of Data and Information:

PipelineDeals may transfer and access certain data and personal information collected from different locations around the world including the United States. This Policy shall apply even if data is transferred and accessed to or from other countries.

If you are located outside of the United States, the personal information that we collect from you will be transferred to, and stored in the United States or another location outside of the EEA. The personal information will also be processed by staff operating in the United States or outside the EEA working for us, other members of our group or third party data processors. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the provision of our services to you, the processing of transactions and/or the provision of support services. By providing us with your personal information you acknowledge any such transfer, storage and processing.

We will always take steps to ensure that such transfers comply with applicable privacy laws and we will take all reasonable precautions to ensure that your personal information is treated securely and in accordance with this Policy.

### How We Keep Your Information Secure:

PipelineDeals has implemented appropriate organizational and technical measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access including a secure, encrypted connection (called an SSL connection) on all pages where you transmit personal data to us. Whenever you access any of your account pages or change any of your user information, it is done over an SSL connection to PipelineDeals. All data transfer to (upload) or from (download) our website will be via over a SSL connection using a current certificate.

In addition, your data is stored at our secure data centers. We maintain our servers in secure data centers in two (2) separate geographical locations. The data centers are staffed twenty four (24) hours per day, seven (7) days per week. Your data is replicated in both data centers in real-time thus always providing a redundant backup of your data in the event that the Service should fail.

In addition, if the redundant servers should fail, PipelineDeals backs up data every four (4) hours to a separate backup production facility.

If you sign up on our website, you will create your own log in id and password that is known only to you and PipelineDeals. PipelineDeals strongly discourages the sharing of your login id and password with anyone. You, the Account Holder, are responsible for the safety and security of your login id and password.

### Retention of Personal Information

There are two types of personal information collected in the PipelineDeals CRM. First, we collect our customer contact information during registration in order to maintain our relationship with them and provide our software to them. We delete our customer records after 2 years from the time of subscription cancelation. Our software allows our customers to collect similar types of information about their own customers and enter it into the PipelineDeals CRM. This customer data is deleted 6 months from the time of subscription cancellation.

### Your Rights Relating to Your Personal Information:

You have certain rights in relation to your personal information. If you would like further information in relation to these or would like to exercise any of them, please contact us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#a1c2d4d2d5ceccc4d3c2c0d3c4e1d1c8d1c4cdc8cfc4c5c4c0cdd28fc2cecc) or by calling +1 (866) 702-7303. You have the right to request that we: 

  * provide access to any personal information we hold about you;
  * update any of your personal information which is out of date or incorrect;
  * delete any personal information which we are holding about you;
  * restrict the way that we process your personal information;
  * prevent the processing of your personal information for direct-marketing purposes;
  * provide, or not provide, your personal information to a third party provider of services;
  * provide you with a copy of any personal information which we hold about you; or
  * consider any valid objections which you have to our use of your personal information.

We will consider all such requests and provide our response within a reasonable period (and in any event any time period required by applicable law). Please note, however, that certain personal information may be exempt from such requests in certain circumstances.

You may also update or change your personal information by logging in to [http://www.pipelinedeals.com](http://www.pipelinedeals.com/) with your PipelineDeals login id and password. Click on User Settings to edit your personal information. You may also email us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#5c3f292f283331392e3f3d2e391c2c352c393035323938393d302f723f3331) or call our customer care number at +1 (866) 702-7303 to request any of the above rights relating to any personal information that we hold about you. 

### Changes to Policy:

We will post all changes to this Policy on the PipelineDeals website. Please check for revisions when you visit our website again so that you will always be aware of our policies and any changes that might occur.

### Contact PipelineDeals:

To ask questions or comment about this Privacy Policy or our privacy or security practices, or our use or storage of your personal information, or if you wish to exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal information, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#86e5f3f5f2e9ebe3f4e5e7f4e3c6f6eff6e3eaefe8e3e2e3e7eaf5a8e5e9eb) or +1 (866) 702-7303.
